(Susan:)Well, fine, if everyone wants to
make jokes about our problems,
(Susan:)then I can, too.
(Susan:)Knock, knock.
Who's there?
(Susan:)Our family is an embarrassment.
(Randall:)That's not much of a joke.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Penny:)Listen, Mom, I know you're
nervous, but I promise you,
(Penny:)no one is gonna judge you
or this family.
(Susan:)Oh, I'm sorry.
(Susan:)It's just we're meeting
Leonard's parents
(Susan:)for the first time,
and-and they're academics
and-and intellectuals,
(Susan:)and I don't want them thinking
we're white trash.
Well, what color trash
do you think they'll believe?
(Mary:)How could you think
that I would spend the night
(Mary:)with a man I just met?
(Sheldon:)A man named Jesus convinced you
to build a church in Africa.
(Sheldon:)You're kind of a sucker.
(Leonard:)Well, nothing happened, right?
I-It's over.
(Leonard:)Until we get married
a third time,
(Leonard:)you guys will never have
to see each other again.
(Alfred:)Well, you know, actually
that's not the case.
(Alfred:)- Mary may visit me in New York.
- Mm-hmm.
(Mary:)And he's never been to Texas.
(Alfred:)Maybe we meet halfway.